Terry. I had my Cadillac in here one time.
Cadillac?
Yeah. I was told to go to a different location, so I went there, and
I just got the total runaround.
Really?
And I said, "I deliver parts, car parts, and
I come here all the time, and they just comfortable people." But we got along.
I talked to them all the time. I come in just get me a cup of waters and stuff like
that. And when I say I had a problem with my Cadillac, I had an
incident. He said, "Bring it here, maybe we can just check it out." So I took it
out of that shop. Of course, they gave me a hassle about getting it out from out of
their shop. So I brought it here, and I came over here, and then A1
service. Comfortable. They did work.
They was real
pleasant. I wasn't just a PO number, a needy, a project for.
Yeah.
I was a customer. I was a friend. I was everything above
that. So I do recommend Phil. Phil Collision is the best place to
be.
Big difference than the other place.
Oh, way big difference. I knew I'm going to be in order or something like
that. I'm going to have to wait for stuff like always time.
Just Phil ordered my parts for my car, and he let me know was everything was set up
and I bring my car in. When I came in there, it was done at the time he said it
would be. So been coming here always, ever since.
Good.
I come in sometimes just to drop in, get me a water.
Just to visit.
Just to visit. Just to visit. They friendly people. I can tell by that spirit.
Nice place.